{
    "id": "201e2609d7f6493a9b976e46d8bc2393",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The event has been ………………………… until next week.",
            "description": "To put off is to postpone.",
            "answers": [
                "put out",
                "put off",
                "put down"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ………………………….. your coat. I am taking you to the doctor.",
            "description": " To put on is to wear",
            "answers": [
                "put on",
                "put out",
                "put in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… the toys once you have finished playing with them.",
            "description": "To put away is to store for future use.",
            "answers": [
                "Put away",
                "Put off",
                "Put in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………………….. the fire in the basement of the building.",
            "description": "To put out is to extinguish.",
            "answers": [
                "put up",
                "put out",
                "put down"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We are planning to ……………………………. a fence around the property.",
            "description": "To put up is to erect.",
            "answers": [
                "put over",
                "put up",
                "put in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. a lot of effort to succeed in her business.",
            "description": "To put in is to invest.",
            "answers": [
                "put up",
                "put in",
                "put out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can no longer ……………………………….. his insolence.",
            "description": "To put up with something is to tolerate it.",
            "answers": [
                "put out with",
                "put up with",
                "put off with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………. the whole neighborhood but nobody had seen my cat.",
            "description": "To ask around is to ask the same question to a lot of people.",
            "answers": [
                "asked around",
                "asked out",
                "asked in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We had a small …………………………… yesterday.",
            "description": "To get together is to meet.",
            "answers": [
                "get off",
                "get together"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The noise …………………………….. after some time.",
            "description": "When noise dies down, it becomes weaker.",
            "answers": [
                "died over",
                "died down"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The scheme ............................... for want of support.",
            "description": "When something falls through, it fails.",
            "answers": [
                "fell off",
                "fell out",
                "fell through"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly the wheel .................................... the bicycle.",
            "description": "To come off is to become detached. ",
            "answers": [
                "came over",
                "came off",
                "came out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}